export const accordians = [

    {
        id: 1,
        question: "What is dyleum?",
        answer: "Dyleum is a decentralized platform that provides a variety of services such as DEX, P2P exchange, Real Estate trading, NFC Payment, DeFi investment pool, Liquidity mining and DApp evaluation program, etc."
    },

    {
        id: 2,
        question: "What can I do with Dyleum?",
        answer: "On Dyleum, you can trade, create, get, sell, and rent real estate with NFT, exchange cryptocurrencies, make payments using NFC, invest in DeFi pools, earn from mining, evaluate DApps and enjoy staking."
    },


    {
        id: 3,
        question: "What are the benefits of using Dyleum?",
        answer: "Dyleum offers secure, transparent, and flexible services with low fees, enabling users to have greater control over their transactions, investments, and liquidity mining operations and also random rewards."
    },


    {
        id: 4,
        question: " How is Dyleum different from other exchanges?",
        answer: "Dyleum is a decentralized platform that offers multiple services as well as a governance system with regulators voting on projects, it also eliminates third party while allowing for NFC and real estate trading."
    },
    {
        id: 5,
        question: "What tokens and coins does Dyleum support?",
        answer: "Dyleum supports multiple cryptocurrencies, traditional payment methods, and stablecoins."
    },
    {
        id: 6,
        question: "How secure is Dyleum?",
        answer: "Dyleum uses smart contracts for secure transactions, transparent and tamper-proof records on the blockchain network, allowing for user-controlled security."
    },
    {
        id: 7,
        question: "What type of fees does Dyleum charge?  ",
        answer: "Dyleum charges lower fees compared to traditional exchanges, 0.01% in token exchange, 5% in investment pool and 0.1% for liquidity mining."
    },
    {
        id: 8,
        question: "How do I get started using Dyleum? ",
        answer: "To start using Dyleum, you need to first connect your wallet on the protocol, then use the supported tokens/coins to start trading or participating in liquidity mining, staking or other features on the platform."
    },
    {
        id: 9,
        question: "What features does Dyleum offer? ",
        answer: "Dyleum offers a variety of features such as trading of various cryptocurrencies, NFTs, and real estate assets, staking, liquidity mining, smart contract based property management, Decentralized DeFi investment pool and DApp evaluation program"
    },

    {
        id: 10,
        question: "How can I contact Dyleum customer support? ",
        answer: "Dyleum offers customer support through their website, social media channels and email. You can also submit a support ticket through their discord."
    },


]